module.exports = {
  nav: [
    {
      name: "About",
      target: "/SET-Hacks/#about"
    },
    {
      name: "Challenges",
      target: "/SET-Hacks/#challenges"
    },
    {
      name: "Sponsors",
      target: "/SET-Hacks/#sponsors"
    },
    {
      name: "FAQ",
      target: "/SET-Hacks/#faq"
    },
    {
      name: "Contact Us",
      target: "/SET-Hacks/contact"
    }
  ],
  date: "Jul 17, 2020 20:00:00",
  socials: [
    {
      platform: "Facebook",
      description: "Add us on Facebook!",
      link: "https://www.facebook.com/setnational/"
    },
    {
      platform: "Instagram",
      description: "Follow our Instagram!",
      link: "https://www.instagram.com/set.ottawa/"
    },
    {
      platform: "Devpost",
      description: "Register on Devpost!",
      link: "https://set-hacks.devpost.com/"
    }
  ],
  aboutQuestions: [
    {
      question: "What is a hackathon?",
      answer: "A hackathon is an invention marathon where you can work with people around the globe to build a project!"
    },
    {
      question: "What is an online hackathon?",
      answer: "It’s an invention marathon like the traditional in-person hackathon, but held remotely!"
    },
    {
      question: "How much does it cost?",
      answer: "SET Hacks is completely free for all participants."
    },
    {
      question: "How long will it run for?",
      answer: "The event will run for 24 hours between July 18th and July 19th."
    },
    {
      question: "Is there a maximum team size?",
      answer: "Yep! Keep your teams to a maximum of 4 people please!"
    },
    {
      question: "What if I don’t have a team?",
      answer: "We will have some online team building sessions, so it doesn’t matter if you’ve not got a team!"
    },
    {
      question: "How do I work with my team?",
      answer: "We strongly suggest that you make a group chat with your team members!"
    }
  ],
  hackingQuestions: [
    {
      question: "Do I need to know how to code?",
      answer: "Nope! If you already know how to code, that\"s great! If not however, this is the perfect time to learn. We will be hosting beginner workshops for you, and we will have experienced mentors to help you with your hacks!"
    },
    {
      question: "Can I work on my hack before the hackathon?",
      answer: "No. In interest of fairness, all hacks must be created at the event."
    },
    {
      question: "Is there stuff to do besides hacking?",
      answer: "We’ll have online workshops, games and other fun activities to keep you busy!"
    },
    {
      question: "What do I need for the hackathon?",
      answer: "The only things you need are a laptop, solid internet connection, and any other materials you may require for creating your hack!"
    },
    {
      question: "Can I volunteer as a mentor or judge?",
      answer: "Yes! SET Hacks wouldn\"t be possible without our volunteers. We will open mentors and judges sign ups soon, so keep an eye open for those!"
    }
  ]
};
